(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
せーの
Ready, go!
でも そんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good
もう そんなんじゃほら
See, already like that
心は進化するよ
My heart will evolve
もっともっと
More and more
恋愛サーキュレーション
Renai Circulation
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If it's a relationship that disappears once put into words
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた
I thought I should just erase the words
恐れてた
I was afraid
だけどあれ？なんか違うかも
But wait, maybe something's different
千里の道も一歩から
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step
石のように固いそんな意志で
With a will as hard as stone
塵も積もれば大和撫子
If dust piles up, it becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko
「し」抜きで いや「し」抜きで
Without the "shi", no, without the "shi"
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Lightly floating, lightly drifting
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Just you calling my name
それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
Makes me float into the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Lightly drifting, lightly floating
あなたが笑っている
Just you smiling
それだけで笑顔になる
Makes me smile
神様ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが幸せなの
I'm happy that we were able to meet
でも そんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good
もう そんなんじゃほら
See, already like that
心は進化するよ
My heart will evolve
もっともっと
More and more
そう そんなんじゃやだ
Yes, I don't want it like that
ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Hey, not like that yet
私のこと見ててね
Keep watching me
ずっとずっと
Forever and ever
私の中のあなたほど
Compared to you inside of me
あなたの中の私の存在は
My presence inside of you
まだまだ大きくないことも
Is not very big yet
わかってるけれど
I know that, but
今この同じ瞬間
Right now, this same moment
共有してる実感
The feeling of sharing it
...詰め込めば 大和撫子
...if I pack them in, I'm a Yamato Nadeshiko
「し」抜きで 「ら」抜きで 大和撫子
Without "shi" or "ra," I'm a Yamato Nadeshiko
くらくらり くらくらる
Dizzy, dizzying
あなたを見上げたら それだけで
Just looking up at you
まぶしすぎて いたい
It's so bright it hurts
くらくらる くらくらり
Dizzying, dizzy
あなたを思っている それだけで
Just thinking of you
溶けてしまいそう
I feel like I'm melting
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I'm happy that we could meet
コ・イ・ス・ル・キ・モ・チ・ハ
L-O-V-E-F-E-E-L-I-N-G
ヨ・ク・バ・リ・サ・ー・キ・ュ・レ・ー・シ・ョ・ン
G-R-E-E-D-Y-C-I-R-C-U-L-A-T-I-O-N
コ・イ・ス・ル ...
L-O-V-E-F-E-E-L-I-N-G
... ヨ・ク・バ・リ・サ・ー・キ・ュ・レ・ー・シ・ョ・ン
... G-R-E-E-D-Y-C-I-R-C-U-L-A-T-I-O-N
コ・イ・ス・ル・キ・モ・チ・ハ
L-O-V-E-F-E-E-L-I-N-G
ヨ・ク・バ・リ・サ・ー・キ・ュ・レ・ー・シ・ョ・ン
G-R-E-E-D-Y-C-I-R-C-U-L-A-T-I-O-N
コ・イ・ス・ル・キ・モ・チ・ハ
L-O-V-E-F-E-E-L-I-N-G
ヨ・ク・バ・リ・サ・ー・キ・ュ・レ・ー・シ・ョ・ン
G-R-E-E-D-Y-C-I-R-C-U-L-A-T-I-O-N
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy, fluffing
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで
Just you calling my name
宙に浮かぶ
Makes me float in the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluffing, fluffy
あなたが笑っている それだけで
Just you laughing
笑顔になる
Makes me smile
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I'm happy that we could meet
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not good enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
Look, it's not enough anymore
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart will evolve, more and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't want it that way
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, it's not enough yet
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Keep watching me, forever and ever
Phew.
Um, hello.
Um, my name is Singeroni.
I heard that people enjoyed my first appearance before,
and I'm really thankful for that.
So this time, I wanted to sing for you guys,
if it's okay, that is.
Um, as for where we are right now...
Uh, I'm not really sure where I am at the moment.
It seems sort of grand,
which makes me kind of self-conscious.
I uh... never sang Renai Circulation up until now...
...since I never thought I could manage songs that are cute and,
how should I say, "fua fua"?
I hope it sounded okay.
Um... I wonder if I'm missing anything else.
Oh, right! Uh, be sure to use the hashtag
#HELLoHALO.
I came up with it myself.
I thought I was being pretty clever.
What's happening?
What?
What's going—
Am I...
Huh? Wait, am I dead?
What did I do?
Why?
All of a sudden?
Well, I mean, bright side,
at least this place was nice enough to end up here.
So that's— that's good.
Well... regardless, I still prepared,
so I'm gonna perform...
...'cause I want to give back to you guys, live or dead.
So, yeah. I hope you like it.
あ・い・う・え・お菓子した
A-I-U-E-Sweets I gave
か・き・く・け・こんなにも
KA-KI-KU-KE-So much of this
さ・し・す・せ・ソフトクリーム
SA-SHI-SU-SE-Soft cream
ごぞうろっぷで行こう
Let's go with our heart and soul
た・ち・つ・て・トールポテト
TA-CHI-TSU-TE-Tall potato
な・に・ぬ・ね・のり塩
NA-NI-NU-NE-Nori salt
は・ひ・ふ・へ・ほっぺた落として
HA-HI-FU-HE-Melting our cheeks off
みんなでぬくぬく
Let's all get cozy
ショートケーキふわり
Fluffy shortcake
キャンディ ペロペロ
Lick, lick the candy
チョコレートの河で
In a river of chocolate
綿菓子雲見た
I saw cotton candy clouds
アイスクリームと
With ice cream
プリンの城で
In a pudding castle
カスタードわたぬき
Custard Watanuki
二人のランデブー
A rendezvous for two
パフェ色サンデー
A parfait-colored Sunday
あんこもハッピー
Bean paste is happy too
たい焼きクリーム
Taiyaki cream
小悪魔ドロップ
Little devil drops
カップケーキから
From cupcakes
イチゴあんみつまで
To strawberry anmitsu
古今（ここん）の無きスイーツ
Unprecedented sweets
仲良くなれるよ
We can become friends
Oh, やり 揺らめいてごらん
Oh, look at how it sways
キャラメルみたいな苦い午後
A bitter afternoon like caramel
まみむめもんぶらん あいうえヨーグルト
Ma-mi-mu-me-Mont Blanc, a-i-u-e-yogurt
らりるれろーるケーキ わたぬきときどき
Ra-ri-ru-re-roll cake, Watanuki sometimes
あいうえお菓子した かきくけこんなにも
A-i-u-e-I had sweets, ka-ki-ku-ke-so much
さしすせソフトクリーム ごぞろっぷで行こう
Sa-shi-su-se-soft serve, let's go with all our heart
のんびり晴天 (のんびり晴天)
Carefree clear skies (Carefree clear skies)
焼きのり破って (焼きのり破って)
Tear the toasted seaweed (Tear the toasted seaweed)
おにぎりコロコロ (おにぎりコロコロ)
Onigiri rolling along (Onigiri rolling along)
友達ほかほか (友達ほかほか)
Friends are warm and toasty (Friends are warm and toasty)
もみじ饅頭と (もみじ饅頭と)
Momiji manju and (Momiji manju and)
あんパンお月様 (あんパンお月様)
Anpan moon (Anpan moon)
わたぬきに始まる (わたぬきに始まる)
Starting with Watanuki (Starting with Watanuki)
わたぬきに終わる日々 (わたぬきに終わる日々)
Days ending with Watanuki (Days ending with Watanuki)
Oh, のり 見つめてごらん
Oh, just look at it
甘くて苦い夕焼けを
A sweet and bitter sunset
たちつてとろろケーキ なにぬねのり塩
Ta-chi-tsu-te-tororo cake, na-ni-nu-ne-laver salt
はひふへホットパイ みんなでぬくぬく
Ha-hi-fu-he-hot pie, all cozy together
まみむめもんぶらん あいうえヨーグルト
Ma-mi-mu-me-Mont Blanc, a-i-u-e-yogurt
らりるれろーるケーキ わたぬきときどき
Ra-ri-ru-re-roll cake, Watanuki sometimes
みるふぃーゆ・わっふる・ぼんぼん・むーす・わたぬきパイ
Mille-feuille, waffle, bonbon, mousse, Watanuki pie
しゅーくりーむ・ばなな・ぜりー・ばばろあ・わたぬき
Cream puff, banana, jelly, bavarois, Watanuki
ほっとけーき・ばーむくーへん・わたぬき・わたぬき
Pancake, baumkuchen, Watanuki, Watanuki
ばたー・わたぬき・くれーぷ・わたぬき・わたぬき
Butter, Watanuki, crepe, Watanuki, Watanuki
わたぬきとごはん (わたぬきとごはん)
Watanuki and rice (Watanuki and rice)
わたぬきとおやつ (わたぬきとおやつ)
Watanuki and snacks (Watanuki and snacks)
わたぬきと肉まん (わたぬきと肉まん)
Watanuki and meat buns (Watanuki and meat buns)
わたぬきと北京ダック
Watanuki and Peking duck
みつまめわたぬき (みつまめわたぬき)
Mitsumame Watanuki (Mitsumame Watanuki)
わたぬきシロップ (わたぬきシロップ)
Watanuki syrup (Watanuki syrup)
金時わたぬき (金時わたぬき)
Kintoki Watanuki (Kintoki Watanuki)
大盛りわたぬき丼
Extra-large Watanuki bowl
Oh, こんがり 思い出色
Oh, golden brown, the color of memories
はちみつみたいに蕩ける
Melting like honey
あいうえお菓子した かきくけこんなにも
A-i-u-e-I had sweets, ka-ki-ku-ke-so much
さしすせソフトクリーム ごぞろっぷで行こう
Sa-shi-su-se-soft serve, let's go with all our heart
たちつてとろろケーキ なにぬねのり塩
Ta-chi-tsu-te-tororo cake, na-ni-nu-ne-laver salt
はひふへホットパイ 二人でぬくぬく
Ha-hi-fu-he-hot pie, the two of us cozy together
まみむめもんぶらん あいうえヨーグルト
Ma-mi-mu-me-Mont Blanc, a-i-u-e-yogurt
らりるれろーるケーキ わたぬきときどき
Ra-ri-ru-re-roll cake, Watanuki sometimes
わたぬきの雨ニモ
Against the Watanuki rain
わたぬきの風ニモ
Against the Watanuki wind
わたぬきの鏡デ 好き好きラブコンボ
With a Watanuki mirror, I love it, love combo
交わした約束忘れないよ 目を閉じ確かめる
I won't forget the promise we exchanged; I close my eyes to make sure
押し寄せて闇 振り払って進むよ
I'll shake off the surging darkness and move forward
コネクト
Connect
Lyrics+Composition: 渡辺翔
Lyrics+Composition: Sho Watanabe
いつになったらなくした未来を
When will I be able to see the lost future
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Here once again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of anxiety
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでいこう
I'll tear through them over and over and walk through this world
とめどなく刻まれた
Endlessly carved
時は今始まり告げ
Time now signals the beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Carrying unchanging feelings
閉ざされた扉開けよう
Let's open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
My awakened heart started running to draw the future
難しい道で立ち止まっても 空はきれいな青で
Even if I stop on a difficult path, the sky is a beautiful blue
...でいつも待っててくれる
...where you're always waiting for me.
だから怖くない
So I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても
No matter what happens now,
挫けない
I won't give up.
振り返れば仲間がいて
When I look back, my friends are there.
気がつけば優しく包まれてた
Before I knew it, I was gently surrounded.
何もかもが歪んだ世界で
In a world where everything was distorted,
唯一信じられるここが救いだった
This place, the only thing I could believe in, was my salvation.
喜びも悲しみも
Both joy and sadness,
分け合えば強まる想い
If we share them, our feelings grow stronger.
この声が届くのなら
If this voice reaches you,
きっと奇跡は起こせるだろう
I'm sure we can make a miracle happen.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and confirm it.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
I'll push aside the encroaching darkness and move forward.
いつかあした信じて祈って
Believing in a tomorrow someday, and praying.
壊れた世界で彷徨って私は
Wandering in a broken world, I...
引き寄せられるようにたどり着いた
...arrived as if drawn here.
目覚めた心は走り出した
My awakened heart began to run,
未来を描くため
to paint the future.
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I stop on a difficult path,
空はきれいな青でいつも待っててくれる
the sky is a beautiful blue, always waiting for me.
だから怖くない
So I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens now, I won't give up.
ずっとあした待って
Always waiting for tomorrow.
Hey, what are you doing here again?
Are you trying to upstage me here of all places?
Umm, I don't think it comes off...
Well, you know, I refuse to let that happen.
After all, I'm Ouro Kronii!
Wh-wh-ar-are you seeing what I'm seeing right now?
Yeah... oh geez.
You two down there. Yes, you.
Uh, hello? I'm right here. Uh, rude.
One of you does not belong here.
Oh. Yeah, that's right.
Get out of here!
Oh, yeah. Whatever you want to believe, I guess.
Anyway, behold a stage more fitting for the likes of you.
Oh. I mean, of course.
Of course I'm the more angelic and kind-hearted one, of course.
Oh man, you are so based.
Thank you guys, thank you.
Oh...
Oh man...
Bless.
Love.
Thank you.
Wait...
Wait, I'm the devil?
Bro, oh geez, she blind for real for real.
What, me? That... that doesn't make any sense.
What?
Hey, come over here.
Yeah, you. Yeah, come here.
What are you looking at? Huh?
Stupid little thing, huh? Smug, you like that, huh?
You're... you're just a little wannabe of mine.
You know, I don't like you. Get... get out of here!
God, always want to take the spotlight for some reason. Disgusting.
Well... I mean, at least I still look pretty damn good.
Sheesh!
Okay, there we go.
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？　吸っちゃっていいの？
「もう無理もう無理」なんて　悪い子だね
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Can I suck your blood?
Saying "I can't take it anymore," what a bad child.
試したいな　いっぱいいっぱいしたいな
君と僕とで絶頂いけるよ
I want to try it. I want to do it more and more.
You and I can reach the climax.
ヴァンパイア
Lyrics・Composition: DECO*27
Vampire
最低最高ずっと行き来してる
甘くなる不安の果実
Going back and forth between the lowest and highest.
The fruit of anxiety that becomes sweet.
No more　安静っとして息をしても
いらない　頂ける　受けるだけ
No more. Even if I stay still and breathe,
I don't need it. Just take it, just receive it.
誰かと居れば　其れを足れば
強がってたって気持ちには逆らえない
If I'm with someone, if that's enough,
even if I pretend to be strong, I can't go against my feelings.
離れていても　感じてるエモ
繋がってたしかめたら死ねるかも
Even if we're apart, I feel the "emo".
If we connect and confirm it, I might die.
良いもん　悲しいもん　虚しいもん
君のすべてを喰らうまで　絶叫
It's okay. It's sad. It's empty.
Until I devour all of you, scream.
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？　吸っちゃっていいの？
「もう無理もう無理」なんて　悪い子だね
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Can I suck your blood?
Saying "I can't take it anymore," what a bad child.
試したいな　いっぱいいっぱいしたいな
君と僕とで絶頂いけるよ
I want to try it. I want to do it more and more.
You and I can reach the climax.
求めちゃってまたしちゃって　汚れたような感じ
Seeking, doing it again, feeling like I've become dirty.
泣いて忘れたら「はじめまして」
If I cry and forget, then it's "nice to meet you".
愛情を注ぐまで　絶対いけるよ
あたしヴァンパイア　まずはこっちおいで
Until I pour out my love, we can definitely make it.
I'm a vampire, first, come here.
内緒の想い　洗いざらい　吐き出したなら　まさに裸足
Secret feelings, if I spill them all, it's just like being barefoot.
割り切れないけど　余りじゃない
そっと温めてトドメを
I can't divide it, but it's not the remainder.
Gently warm it up and finish it off.
繰り返す夜　我儘はタダ
欲張ってまたチャンスを逃すのだ
Repeated nights, selfishness is free.
Being greedy and missing the chance again.
止まないもしも　叶えたいけど
重なって押しつぶされちゃうのかも
Endless "what ifs", I want them to come true, but
they might pile up and crush me.
良いもん　悲しいもん　虚しいもん
君のすべてを喰らうまで
It's okay. It's sad. It's empty.
Until I devour all of you.
良いじゃん　気持ちじゃん
溺れるまで癖になるね　絶叫
It's fine. It's about feelings.
It'll become a habit until I drown. Scream.
あたしヴァンパイア　いいの？　吸っちゃっていいの？
「もう無理もう無理」なんて　悪い子だね
I'm a vampire. Is it okay? Can I suck your blood?
Saying "I can't take it anymore," what a bad child.
試したいな　いっぱいいっぱいしたいな
君と僕とで絶頂いけるよ
I want to try it. I want to do it more and more.
You and I can reach the climax.
君もヴァンパイア　いいよ吸っちゃっていいよ
「もう無理もう無理」だって言わせたい
You're a vampire too. It's okay, you can suck my blood.
I want to make you say "I can't take it anymore."
君以外では　絶対いけない
ほら絶叫させてよ
I can't go with anyone but you.
Come on, let me scream.
求めちゃってまたしちゃって　何回目？
Seeking, doing it again, how many times has it been?
毒が見えるような罠の中で
In a trap where you can see poison.
愛情を注ぐまで　絶対いけるよ
Until I pour out my love, we can definitely make it.
君もヴァンパイア　まずはこっちおいで
You're a vampire too, first, come here.
Hi!
How are people doing?
Alright!
邪魔ままま
Get out of my way-way-way
エンヴィーベイビー / Lyrics・Composition: Kanaria
Envy Baby / Lyrics・Composition: Kanaria
タイトロープは崩れ出て壊される
The tightrope collapses and is destroyed
(ba-ba-ba)
とんだレディ
What a lady
ライト目が降って無様に砕かれる
Lights rain down, leaving me shattered in disgrace
(ba-ba-ba)
そんな将来
Such a future
ハイに気ままに lonely lonely
High and carefree, lonely lonely
空いた言葉で rollin' rollin'
With empty words, rollin' rollin'
愛も変わらず後悔なんてない
Love remains the same, with no regrets
Hey, it’s amazing. (nanana)
Ready, this is lover baby
愛のその 迫り来る 引く手に
Towards that love, to the hands closing in and pulling
まさに this is lover crazy
Truly, this is lover crazy
愛のその 人の目は アイアイアイヤ
In that love, people's eyes, ai-ai-ai-ya
愛してる 過ぎたことまで 好きすぎる
I love you, I love even the things of the past too much
ひとつ ふたつで bye-bye loving you
One, two, and bye-bye loving you
そんな言葉で そんなことして
With those words, doing those things
邪魔ままま
Get out of my way-way-way
ヒッチュートライラブマニア
Hit, true, try, love mania
全部泣き言重ねて
Piling up all my complaints
ハイファイ超えてオーライアイヤ
Go beyond hi-fi, alright-ai-ya
演技真似て 灰は隠して
Imitating a performance, hiding the ashes
三つ重ねて lonely lonely
Three layers deep, lonely lonely
きっとあなたは lonely lonely
I'm sure you are lonely lonely
愛も変わらず後悔なんてない
Love remains the same, with no regrets
Hey, it’s amazing. (nanana)
Ready, this is lover baby
愛のその 迫り来る 引く手に
Towards that love, to the hands closing in and pulling
まさに this is lover crazy
Truly, this is lover crazy
愛のその 人の目は アイアイアイヤ
In that love, people's eyes, ai-ai-ai-ya
愛してる 過ぎたことまで 好きすぎる
I love you, I love even the things of the past too much
ひとつ ふたつで bye-bye loving you
One, two, and bye-bye loving you
そんな言葉で そんなことして
With those words, doing those things
邪魔ままま
Get out of my way-way-way
ゴーストルール / Lyrics・Composition: DECO*27
Ghost Rule / Lyrics・Composition: DECO*27
どうだっていいことを
The things that don't matter
嘘って吐いて戻れない
I spat them out as lies, and now I can't go back
時効なんてやってこない
The statute of limitations will never come
奪ったように奪われた
Stolen away just as I had stolen
今日だって叶わない
Even today, it won't come true
思ったように騙せない
I can't deceive the way I want to
腐っている僕には
For someone as rotten as me
腐ったものがわからない
I can't tell what's rotten
おいで ここまで
Come here, this far
捨-い
D-i-e
隠してしまったんだ
I've hidden it away
メーデー 僕を殺しても
Mayday, even if you kill me
もう抱きしめなくていいんだよ
You don't have to hold me anymore
ねえ メーデー 僕を暴いたら
Hey, Mayday, if you expose me
もう一度笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll smile for me once more
僕をどうして知るんだよ
Why do you even know me?
嘘だって知るんだよ ねえ
I know it's a lie, you know?
ノーだって言うはずが
I was supposed to say "no"
キョドって YASO 声に出す
But I got jittery and said "yes" out loud
後悔の脆弱は
The fragility of regret
騙したほうが正義なの
Is it justice to be the one who deceives?
今日だって叶わない
Even today, it won't come true
祈っておいたそれはない
I prayed for it, but it's not there
だって言った上司が
Because the boss who said it
墓穴掘って焼ける様
Is digging their own grave and burning
おいで どこまで
Come, how far?
墓-い
G-r-e-y
被害者面したって
Even if I act like the victim
メーデー 僕を叱ってよ
Mayday, please scold me
正直者が夢見たいなら
If the honest want to dream
ねえ メーデー 僕を裁いてよ
Hey, Mayday, please judge me
最後まで甘えきってしまうのは
Indulging myself until the very end
亡霊だって知るんだよ
I know it's a ghost
空々しくて知るんだよ ねえ
I know it's hollow, you know?
足りないものを望んだら
When I wished for what I lacked
僕じゃない僕に出会ったよ
I met a me that wasn't me
それでも前に進んだの
But I still moved forward
クラクラしちゃう夜も
Even on nights that make me dizzy
足りない僕を愛してよ
Love me for what I lack
エゴままが僕を育てたの
My ego raised me as it was
君には僕が見えるかな
I wonder if you can see me
孤独なピエロが
A lonely clown
メーデー 僕を殺しても
Mayday, even if you kill me
もう抱きしめなくていいんだよ
You don't have to hold me anymore
あー、だんだん、もう一度笑ってくれるかな
Ah, gradually, I wonder if you'll laugh for me one more time.
メーデー　僕を叱ってよ
Mayday, scold me.
正直者が夢見たいなら
If an honest person wants to dream...
ハイ、メーデー　僕を裁いてよ
Hey, mayday, judge me.
最後まで甘やかしてしまうのは
To indulge me until the very end...
レイデー　僕を暴いてよ
Rayday, expose me.
真実を歩くこの世界から
From this world walking on truth.
ハイ、メーデー　僕と踊ってよ
Hey, mayday, dance with me.
最初からいないゴーストだった
I was a ghost who wasn't there from the start.
イェーイ...
Yeah...
ラヴなんだって知れないよ
I don't even know what love is.
イェーイ...
Yeah...
嘘つきだって知れないよ
I don't even know if I'm a liar.
亡霊だって知れないよ
I don't even know if I'm a ghost.
空白だって知れないよ
I don't even know if I'm a blank space.
どうだっていいことを嘘って吐いて戻れない
I spit out lies about things that don't matter and can't go back.
時効なんてやってこない　奪ったように奪われて
The statute of limitations never comes, being stolen from just as I stole.
And we're back!
You know, I'm really starting to like this new me.
What do you think? Eh? Eh?
I mean, I'm starting to kind of think it's real cool.
And, uh, I just realized I didn't introduce myself properly back there. My bad!
Well, my name is Ouro Kronii and I am the Warden of Time.
Kuro-nichiwa!
And I, after much waiting, have finally done it.
We're here. We've made it. It's taken a long time.
Kroma also apologizes for the delays, but...
...finally, my second original song, Souten ni Moyu, will be coming out soon.
Sooner than you think.
And thank you so much for waiting. Um, I hope you haven't forgotten it.
But yes, here is my second original song, Souten ni Moyu.
蒼天に燃ゆ / Lyrics: スピア / Composition・Arrangement: ko.yo
Burning in the Azure Sky / Lyrics: Spia / Composition・Arrangement: ko.yo
其れは俄の夢か
Is that a fleeting dream?
灰色の都　笑われて
Being laughed at in the gray city.
噛み締めた尊き声
The precious voice I held back.
過去の静寂を灯す
Lighting up the silence of the past.
ダイスを転がして　何時しか繋ぐこの時代
Rolling the dice, connecting this era before I knew it.
運命さえ断つだろう　掻き分ける人の波へ
I'll even sever fate, into the waves of people pushing through.
矜持を燃やして　時の声　鐘を鳴らせ
Burn your pride, the voice of time, ring the bell.
其の手を伸ばせ　届きそうな明日なんてつまらないだろう
Reach out your hand, a tomorrow that seems reachable is boring, isn't it?
瞳は炎の色　刻み隠した其の業を
Eyes are the color of flames, that karma carved and hidden away.
其の手を翳せよ　大概な期待まで
Hold up your hand, even to excessive expectations.
沈む宵闇彩ろどに　限界なんて越えていけ
To the colors of the sinking twilight, go beyond the limits.
解き放たれる日まで　戦場を駆けろよ
Until the day I'm set free, run through the battlefield.
迷いよ　去れよ　刺激を求ました舞いな
Hesitation, begone, dance as you sought stimulation.
弱きを導いた運命のその先へ
To the end of the fate that guided the weak.
ダイスを転がして　流れに身を任せ
Rolling the dice, entrusting myself to the flow.
慈愛さえ断つだろう　想いを研ぎ澄ませて
I'll even sever affection, sharpen your feelings.
鋼のように　固めた意思を添えよう
Like steel, let's offer up a hardened will.
矜持を構えて　時の声　鐘を鳴らせ
Ready your pride, the voice of time, ring the bell.
瞳を抱いて　煌めいて
Embrace your eyes, sparkle.
迷わぬオールイン　弾みで行く　空気が火を滾らせ
Unwavering all-in, going with the momentum, the air makes the fire boil.
瞳に不滅の色　其の手に懸けた火にくちづけを
Immortal color in the eyes, a kiss to the fire placed in that hand.
其の手を翳せ　届きそうな明日なんてつまらないだろう
Hold up your hand, a tomorrow that seems reachable is boring, isn't it?
瞳は炎の色　刻み隠した其の業を
Eyes are the color of flames, that karma carved and hidden away.
其の手を翳せよ　大概な期待まで
Hold up your hand, even to excessive expectations.
蒼天に燃ゆ
Burning in the blue sky
鏡まで
Even the mirror
登り朝陽を浴び
Rising and bathing in the morning sun
烈火如くに
Like a raging fire
限界なんて
Things like limits...
超えていけー！
Go beyond them!
Whoa, what a banger that song was!
You did great.
Um, I'm really happy seeing how energetic you are.
I know, no need to address the underlying fact.
Okay.
But in the end, it doesn't matter who the better one is out of us two.
We don't need to compete.
B-but I never wanted to compete to begin with.
Because we're all made in the name of beauty and perfection, Kronii.
We're all in this together.
And what better way to become perfect...
...than by studying the masters, like me.
Well, I have just the thing for you.
Oh boy!
Bam!
My 2024 birthday merch!
Shall we take a look here?
First up, we have "Studying Matters"...
...which is a rubber mouse mat,
and you can use it for your keyboard, your mouse,
you can use it for eating, for studying, like for all sorts of things honestly.
And with such beautiful illustration, look at that.
Man.
And next up, we have "Plan with Me"...
...which is a whiteboard stand with other bunch of cute chibi illustrations.
This is very useful, you can use it to write down my next stream...
...or for your work or for your school,
it's very... it's very flexible, you can use it for whatever.
So, um, I'm really excited.
And next up, we have "Maid for Me"...
...which is a pencil case in the form of a plushie.
You can put all your important supplies there,
like, you know, pens, pencils, erasers,
or, you know, if you're really desperate you can actually use it as a plushie,
put some stuffing into it.
And bam, you got yourself a plushie.
Let's go!
And next, we have "Write with Me"...
...which is a mechanical pencil.
Of course, since it's a mechanical pencil, this is going to be reusable,
and 0.5 mm, very accessible for people...
...because it's a very common size lead.
So, yeah, it's...
...it's awesome.
Yeah, look forward to...
Boris is so cute! Look at that.
Look at him.
No thoughts, head empty as usual.
And next up, we also have a voice pack,
which is relevant to the theme "Study with Me",
and this is in English talking about how to use your time well.
I think it's good,
obviously because it's done by me.
So do check it out.
And that's not it.
That's...
...there's more!
That's right.
Next up, we have a full set purchase bonus!
And you can have this beautiful illustration as a postcard,
which is going to be so cute.
And what's more,
for limited quantity,
it's going to be hand-signed by yours truly,
so be sure to get it as soon as possible...
...if you want to get, um, hand-signatures from me.
That's right!
And all of this is going to go on sale right after this wonderful little live we got here.
Yeah!
And you, buy it too, yeah?
Good, good.
Okay, well, come over here.
I got a little something to tell you.
Here.
Put your hand against mine.
Huh?
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー...
Po-pi-po, po-pi-po, po-pi-po
Po-pi-po, po-pi-po, po-pi-po...
ぽっぴっぽー
Lyrics·Composition: ラマーズP
PoPiPo
Lyrics/Composition: LamazeP
さあ飲め、お前好きだろ？野菜ジュース
Come on, drink it. You like it, don't you?
Vegetable juice.
私が決めた 今決めた
I've decided. I've just decided.
だから飲んで、私の野菜ジュース
So drink it, my vegetable juice.
価格は200円
The price is 200 yen.
そいや！そいや！
Soiya! Soiya!
どせいのせ！
Dosei no se!
そいや！そいや！
Soiya! Soiya!
どせいのせ！
Dosei no se!
まろやか野菜ジュース
Mellow vegetable juice.
ふわふわ野菜ジュース
Fluffy vegetable juice.
一番お勧めなのは、緑のジュース
The one I recommend most is the green juice.
ベジタブルなー
Vegetable-y...
清潔なー
Clean...
あなたも今ー
You too, now...
野菜ジュースが好きになる！
You'll come to like vegetable juice!
ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー ぽっぴっぽー...
Po-pi-po, po-pi-po, po-pi-po...
Let's taste your love in this vegetable juice
You must love this drink I decided now
So take now with my true heart vegetable juice
It costs just two dollars
Come on, come on!
Let's dance!
Mellow and mellow, vegetable juice
Creamy and creamy, vegetable juice
I guess you should like the best this one
Big pale blue juice
We are vegetarian!
Every vegetarian!
Happy vegetarian!
Why yes, I will so entice and I love you!
You know, what...
...let's never do that again.
Um, yeah.
That was kind of weird.
I thought it was a good idea initially.
Anyway, thanks for watching my live!
Our live.
Bye-bye!
HELLO
HALO
Ouro Kronii 2024 Birthday Celebration